[
  {
    "question": "What are the two components of a sarcomere?",
    "answer": "Actin and myosin",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 5 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "6297ba7c-ae81-44fb-9bef-8537925bf5f8"
  },
  {
    "question": "What surrounds the skeletal muscles and connects them to other surrounding muscles?",
    "answer": "Fascia",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 5 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "dadea19c-45a6-45db-92af-f68f8f1b58d1"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the concept that describes the human body as a chain of interdependent links that work together to perform movement?",
    "answer": "Kinetic chain",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 5 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "865e8c2b-55be-45fa-81a7-7dabe017dd40"
  },
  {
    "question": "When a client's heart rate is raised during cardio activities, this is being caused by which system?",
    "answer": "Sympathetic nervous system",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 5 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "34e3a91d-ab01-4122-a66d-b468339312e0"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is the functional unit of a muscle cell?",
    "answer": "A sarcomere",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 5 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "af3da97a-2b36-4888-b156-c2dfbe01e9d3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the function of the neuromuscular junction?",
    "answer": "The site where the nervous system and muscle fibers communicate",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 5 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "298e103b-1359-4b67-a50a-33807f190a0e"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which system supplies neural input to organs that run the involuntary processes of the body?",
    "answer": "Autonomic nervous system",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 5 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "b996e23f-38bf-4d4a-9be7-9a774ff24bc2"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the specialized cell that is the functional unit of the nervous system?",
    "answer": "Neuron",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 5 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "fbb15f10-d39d-4cf2-8304-eafc28d4c5df"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which mechanoreceptor is sensitive to changes in muscular tension and rate of that tension change, causing the muscle to relax, which prevents the muscle from excessive stress and possible injury?",
    "answer": "Golgi tendon organs",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 5 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "b129c800-2c3f-4e1e-91f1-ea99cd8eee25"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which system supplies neural input to organs that run the involuntary processes of the body?",
    "answer": "Autonomic nervous system",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 5 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "97ea58de-93fc-442f-9c90-72e6a24ff0d4"
  },
  {
    "question": "At what age is the adolescent brain considered to be fully developed?",
    "answer": "25",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 5 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "dfde36de-a898-48ae-9af3-149af7899a3a"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which joints are most associated with human movement?",
    "answer": "Synovial",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 5 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "32da2a07-72f8-405d-8c62-215a8322828e"
  },
  {
    "question": "At what age is total peak bone mass reached?",
    "answer": "30",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 5 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "786ad615-3bde-4a73-a050-9b1c26c1280d"
  },
  {
    "question": "What effect of the cardiovascular system occurs during exercise?",
    "answer": "Increased ventricular filling",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 6 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "1d9db444-fe1d-427c-8c01-5a08f234dd4e"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is cardiac output?",
    "answer": "The volume of blood pumped by the heart per minute",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 6 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "7702dee7-cdd4-4fcc-97a1-437bc5ae772b"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which heart chamber gathers deoxygenated blood returning to the heart from the superior and inferior vena cava veins?",
    "answer": "Right atrium",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 6 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "34c60c9b-eef7-4ac1-9721-a5a73971c1cb"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which heart chamber gathers oxygenated blood coming to the heart from the lungs?",
    "answer": "Left atrium",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 6 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "e6fa20d5-31dd-4f9c-920e-9ba3c3d68ebd"
  },
  {
    "question": "What component of breathing improves blood flow back to the heart?",
    "answer": "Inspiration with a decrease in intrathoracic pressure",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 6 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "999860b3-b3a9-41b9-87c2-509420508104"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is end-diastolic volume?",
    "answer": "The amount of blood in the ventricle before contraction",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 6 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "0b5d7dfd-0d18-4b88-b6d0-7ae19aa33390"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where in the digestive system are most fluids absorbed?",
    "answer": "Small Intestine",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 6 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "8855c188-a02d-4b36-9cd8-3900a4ab7e64"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which type of exercise accommodates effort whereby the harder the individual pushes or pulls, the more resistance they feel, despite the movement speed remaining constant?",
    "answer": "Isokinetic",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 7 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "972ffae0-9941-4ed4-a71c-2c952e0a65d7"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the most accurate description of motor control?",
    "answer": "The ability to initiate and correct purposeful controlled movements",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 7 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "87128da8-91b8-4896-a5ea-ef7f4a804413"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the anatomical term that describes something positioned above an identified reference point?",
    "answer": "Superior",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 7 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "6e6872ae-abaf-477b-8479-db5c262393ea"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the anatomical term that describes something positioned below an identified reference point?",
    "answer": "Inferior",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 7 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "25f878e8-a75a-43cb-bfaa-dd3026474706"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the anatomical term that describes something positioned to the front of identified reference point?",
    "answer": "Anterior",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 7 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "baf57786-505e-40a8-93af-f67f60afeff9"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the anatomical term that describes something positioned to the back of identified reference point?",
    "answer": "Posterior",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 7 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "51df43cf-4beb-40d7-8946-517eb102b637"
  },
  {
    "question": "Overactive hip flexors may lead to which of the following postural compensations?",
    "answer": "Anterior tilting of the pelvis and an increased low-back arch",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 7 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "ea4f5f86-6a6b-4deb-931e-3c4b0924b4af"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following muscle groups work both eccentrically and concentrically in the sagittal plane during a squat?",
    "answer": "Quadriceps",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 7 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "b0d54b1a-d8d4-482a-9057-bc745a084a18"
  },
  {
    "question": "Movements that take place within a joint and are not visible to the human eye may be classified in what way?",
    "answer": "Arthrokinematic",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 7 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "13a9f6ca-c96c-464f-a7f4-b50057aea4b0"
  },
  {
    "question": "How should an eccentric muscle action be described?",
    "answer": "The development of muscle tension during lengthening of the contractile tissue",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 7 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "740996ff-5bda-4836-8fbc-39d1788cf191"
  },
  {
    "question": "Stored energy from an efficiently functioning stretch-shortening cycle is released during which muscle action?",
    "answer": "Concentric",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 7 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "84960557-0500-4e9b-9664-461d1bf898a3"
  },
  {
    "question": "In what plane of movement do shoulder horizontal adduction and abduction occur?",
    "answer": "Transverse",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 7 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "db4ffd45-6711-4eed-8ffd-ccfffc5becb0"
  },
  {
    "question": "What scientific term is used to describe the concept whereby a loaded eccentric contraction prepares the muscles for a rapid concentric contraction?",
    "answer": "Stretch-shortening cycle",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 7 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "debce03d-f0fe-47fe-9872-a27439645cb8"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the anatomical term that describes something positioned on the opposite side of the body?",
    "answer": "Contralateral",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 7 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "9a3209ed-f6b9-4298-98b6-17d4b9d96aa0"
  },
  {
    "question": "What measurement is dependent upon the length of the lever arm and the angle between the force application and the lever arm?",
    "answer": "Torque",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 7 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "2dcd60cd-b562-433b-baf0-99a5c5271c5f"
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of lever could be described as having a fulcrum in the middle like a seesaw?",
    "answer": "First Class",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 7 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "819afcd7-8dfa-48b1-96eb-1bd9a4a394d3"
  },
  {
    "question": "Pronation of the foot describes what multiplanar movements?",
    "answer": "Eversion, dorsiflexion, and ankle abduction",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 7 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "047edbe4-7ac9-4c21-928f-87bce625584c"
  },
  {
    "question": "During normal walking, the pelvis rotates in what plane to facilitate the necessary momentum for the swing phase?",
    "answer": "Transverse",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 7 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "3ee94f36-9ee8-4ee7-9fde-4f53bb10add3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the scientific term that describes the nervous systemâ€™s role in the contract/relax relationship between agonists and antagonists?",
    "answer": "Reciprocal inhibition",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 7 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "dd90b8ed-263b-4d9e-8fd7-1420d831e60d"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following statements would be accurate with regard to muscle force and velocity during an eccentric muscle action?",
    "answer": "As the contraction velocity increases the ability to develop force also increases.",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 7 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "aa7afff9-a179-478a-9ae1-3bdf635274b5"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the concept used to describe the action of muscles that have the ability to contract automatically in anticipation of movement?",
    "answer": "Feed-forward",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 7 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "f5373959-e06e-43ba-ac6e-65c2cbd0896f"
  },
  {
    "question": "If someone were performing repeated sprints with each sprint lasting between 30 and 90 seconds, which energy system would be contributing the most to ATP production during this activity?",
    "answer": "Glycolysis",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 8",
      "section 3"
    ],
    "id": "8a48ad66-0e01-443e-b262-f5086e02b9a6"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the only way that mass is lost when a person loses body weight?",
    "answer": "As exhaled carbon dioxide",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 8 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "8944dc6c-cf65-47e2-84c1-9f8f2721adfd"
  },
  {
    "question": "Why is nonexercise activity thermogenesis (NEAT) important?",
    "answer": "NEAT can be protective against obesity.",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 8 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "1f73908a-1582-42f8-8564-16c2e172df36"
  },
  {
    "question": "What two factors define any form or type of exercise?",
    "answer": "Intensity and duration",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 8 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "4a2e3fe7-d040-429b-8181-e01c3c6a14b9"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are triglycerides?",
    "answer": "The stored form of fat",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 8 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "4b64659b-b302-4dc9-8b19-b95a748be839"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which energy system would provide most of the ATP for someone on a 5-mile jog?",
    "answer": "Oxidative phosphorylation",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 8 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "3eb113c0-e811-4d4b-abfc-661523067b0b"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a ketone body?",
    "answer": "Acetoacetic acid, BHB",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 8 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "f0819b10-9f1f-4d2c-9f80-f389c1c0beee"
  },
  {
    "question": "Food is composed of which three compounds?",
    "answer": "Carbohydrates, fats, and proteins",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 8 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "616969c1-8e7f-46f9-aaf2-5182cf23378b"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the first law of thermodynamics state?",
    "answer": "Energy can neither be created nor destroyed.",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 8 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "76fc0919-0fb6-4227-947d-138d0a3a52b4"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which nutrient has the highest thermic effect?",
    "answer": "Protien",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 8 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "eda4c0b9-6c8f-40b1-90fd-d9867380f298"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is defined as steady-state exercise?",
    "answer": "Aerobic exercise performed at a constant intensity",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 8 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "c07a6d9d-d7e9-47b6-acce-cfef5e976ac0"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the process called when ADP is converted to ATP?",
    "answer": "Phosphorylation",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 8 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "5501f73b-0b2a-443b-8afb-4aad67d91116"
  },
  {
    "question": "Before carbohydrates, fat, or protein can enter the citric acid cycle (CAC), they need to be converted to what common molecule?",
    "answer": "Acetyl CoA",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 8 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "c30b08dc-cacb-4fd9-ab11-b616dbede59f"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the electron transport chain (ETC) do?",
    "answer": "The ETC uses a hydrogen gradient to create ATP.",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 8 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "c3e63c36-8cc5-4fdb-b4fe-66bbb7ed934c"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the ventilatory threshold 1 (VT1)?",
    "answer": "The point at which the body switches to using carbohydrates to provide at least half the fuel for exercise",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 8 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "d291c195-95e7-480f-88d3-1c80dbc90842"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a kilocalorie (kcal)?",
    "answer": "The amount of energy needed to raise 1 kilogram of water by 1 degree Celsius. It is also the same thing as 1 food calorie.",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 8 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "dcace9e4-96d8-4baf-85db-60c5d6235a95"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a limiting factor for how long anaerobic glycolysis can proceed?",
    "answer": "Free hydrogen ions",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 8 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "cc14b19e-f9ad-427c-a696-f53e47a745f6"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is excess postexercise oxygen consumption (EPOC)?",
    "answer": "EPOC is the increase in aerobic metabolism above baseline that occurs for a period after exercise.",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 8 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "2d250de8-bfce-4231-9c5b-e61283172c90"
  },
  {
    "question": "What would make a person better at oxidizing fat?",
    "answer": "Having more mitochondria in their muscle",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 8 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "eebb72a5-a878-4e16-a21e-f49efb008512"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which energy system would occur during intermittent exercise?",
    "answer": "All three energy systems would be used at some point during the activity.",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 8 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "ab727832-4e73-4c28-9f83-de13190ebc98"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are essential amino acids?",
    "answer": "Amino acids that must be consumed because they cannot be created by the body",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 8 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "dcd9964a-316e-46a0-b925-d57bf9bae9f1"
  },
  {
    "question": "What process do amino acids have to go through before they can be used to make ATP?",
    "answer": "Gluconeogenesis",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 8 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "442a4652-99c3-49d4-9fb4-913eeef946d2"
  },
  {
    "question": "What will happen to pyruvate if it is being created via glycolysis faster than oxygen can be delivered to the muscle?",
    "answer": "The pyruvate will be converted to lactate.",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 8 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "0465dffb-b73a-4186-b26c-4e8e8cf4aa97"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the stored form of glucose?",
    "answer": "Glycogen",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 8 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "3d99e565-e4ef-4373-9e73-a445f7dbf8e1"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the definition of energy balance?",
    "answer": "When daily food intake is matched to energy needs",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 8 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "2e94cd24-f389-46a6-9436-9f5fbb2683a9"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following conditions would produce nutritional ketosis in the body?",
    "answer": "A very low-carbohydrate diet",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 8 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "3c92d9c1-1d58-48c9-90f0-de623980049c"
  },
  {
    "question": "A client plans to go for a 10-mile run, but they become fatigued after 7 miles, so they stop. What is the most likely cause of this fatigue?",
    "answer": "Glycogen stores were exhausted.",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 8 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "29d74e51-b30b-4566-8495-f8a306144502"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following components of total daily energy expenditure (TDEE) is responsible for the most energy expenditure throughout the day?",
    "answer": "Resting metabolic rate (RMR)",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 8 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "983a3fd8-64b5-4b36-97d7-31a9ec57556e"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is bioenergetics?",
    "answer": "The study of the ways in which food is turned into energy",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 8 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "2ab13eb8-897b-4b1d-90f6-ad323c12e35a"
  },
  {
    "question": "A client who is training with you to improve his body composition states that he only sleeps 4 or 5 hours a night because he thinks that any more is a waste of time. How might you respond to him in view of his body composition goals?",
    "answer": "Explain that adequate sleep is important in regulating hunger and satiety hormones, and that chronic sleep deprivation is detrimental for weight management.",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 9 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "f38414ed-6f83-439a-b87a-0a0855c02208"
  },
  {
    "question": "Apart from energy intake and physical activity, which of the following factors also influence weight management?",
    "answer": "Hormones and medications",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 9 quiz",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "48549ba2-d099-40a1-9f3e-186853e09f97"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the three categories within the lipid family?",
    "answer": "Triglycerides, phospholipids, and sterols",
    "id": "b3cdbb9a-8f20-4e7c-9d61-afcb3fa3d5d1"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the optimal amount of protein per meal for muscle protein synthesis?",
    "answer": "20 to 40 g",
    "id": "cb49d8e7-1a1a-4a25-9067-23aae3b1a9ab"
  },
  {
    "question": "According to current research, what is the optimal range of daily protein intake to maximize muscle protein synthesis?",
    "answer": "1.6 to 2.2 g/kg of body weight",
    "id": "3f58c70f-73f9-426b-8751-42246f9174b5"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the macronutrients has the highest thermic effect of food (TEF)?",
    "answer": "Protien",
    "id": "d875af5f-f1b2-4f8b-8dde-5e5c0a8214e5"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following vitamins or groups of vitamins plays a key role in energy metabolism?",
    "answer": "B Vitamins",
    "id": "c0daa4c4-f08f-4bd9-899c-f3f396e65e85"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is adaptive thermogenesis?",
    "answer": "Metabolic adaptations and changes in energy expenditure due to changes in energy intake",
    "id": "eba213c1-4be8-4ee8-b705-d1b87849e8ea"
  },
  {
    "question": "Accumulating too much of a vitamin or mineral in the body may lead to what?",
    "answer": "Toxicity",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 10",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "49bcc4db-8d1f-42b7-9469-cf3f97b5ec72"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is true about the biologically active forms of vitamins?",
    "answer": "Biologically active forms are most effective for augmenting body levels.",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 10",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "819892c7-08a2-4289-95c5-cbf2c2d90333"
  },
  {
    "question": "The water-soluble vitamins include which vitamins?",
    "answer": "Vitamin C and the B complex vitamins",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 10",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "41ca0f1c-8747-442c-b7ec-6b39e0ec804a"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is true of protein shakes?",
    "answer": "They are convenient options for increasing protein intake.",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 10",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "6cc6ef02-e6ac-44e5-b474-862e117eb977"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the best definition of essential when discussing human nutrition?",
    "answer": "Must be obtained in the diet, as the body is incapable of producing the nutrient on its own",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 10",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "f8503b08-5f21-410f-8998-17de6083b8b8"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which two electrolytes are most commonly supplemented by athletes to replace those lost in sweat?",
    "answer": "Sodium and potassium",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 10",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "e46e1403-c594-418e-9687-16f9f63d316a"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a major nutritional contributor to muscle protein synthesis?",
    "answer": "The essential amino acids",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 10",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "f85539ef-162f-4beb-95f2-71f2ae197b71"
  },
  {
    "question": "What percentage of alpha-linolenic acid (ALA) converts to a biologically available form called eicosapentaenoic acid (EPA)?",
    "answer": "About 5-15%",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 10",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "bb83b887-02e3-4c43-b110-222203a5cc7c"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which governmental agency regulates dietary supplements in Australia?",
    "answer": "Therapeutic Goods Administration (TGA)",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 10",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "aff28fc4-ec44-4d7f-a0d2-b2b644d8a140"
  },
  {
    "question": "The B vitamins have a primary role in what?",
    "answer": "Macronutrient metabolism",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 10",
      "section 3 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "1752cf12-e840-4f6b-94fc-4d79945a0a30"
  }
]